Hello friends, if you
are really a CSC and you work in insurance,
then let me tell you that if you are
doing any insurance work and due to some
technical problem the saver print is not coming out
or you want to print that print again, then
how will you be
able to do that, you have been told about it in this video,
friends, first of all what will we do is we will
log in to the CSC portal,
here I have logged in my portal
and in it we will search
ICICI, if you have done insurance through ICAI
and you want to take out its
copy, then you can take it out like this,
ICICI Lombard, if we search here, then
first we click on Gaya Motor Third Party, as soon as we
search,
we will be
taken to the homepage of ICICI Lombard and from here you have done
insurance of any vehicle and
its biscuit has not been generated
or
if you want to download the receiver print of the insurance again, then
you can do it easily from here,
what will you have to do first of all, here
you will be seeing my  There is transaction, you have to go here,
after going to the tractor, you have to click on My Life Partner Policy,
after clicking, sir friends, a
small page will open in it, you have to
select get, so we massage here,
I had displayed it in March, we have to
remove it, so we will make it from March 1 to March 31,
we will check the motor in this product and
here you have to pay special attention, sir, if we
update it here in the product, then
it will be displayed, here you have to
click on two wheeler liability and after
clicking on it, click on simple search,
so see in front of us, we did the
same policy here on 3rd and 9th,
so we have to see it, you can see it here
from the previous policy that it came like this,
but we do not have to
see the proposal, we have to keep it in the protected here,
so we will click on policy, so see,
my policy will come like this, now
we will print it, download it, you will
save it in the period, so friends, I hope
that if you liked the information given by me, then
you like my video,
share it and subscribe to my channel  Do
n't forget to do it and if
anything else comes to your mind, please write in the comment box.